{
    "Addition_&_Subtraction": {
        "1": {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "question": "7 + 9 = ?",
                    "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 16
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "question": "3 + 8 = ?",
                    "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 11
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "question": "5 + 10 = ?",
                    "options": [15, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 15
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "question": "6 + 4 = ?",
                    "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 10
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "question": "14 - 6 = ?",
                    "options": [8, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 8
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "question": "10 - 7 = ?",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "question": "3 - 1 = ?",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "question": "9 - 4 = ?",
                    "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 5
                }
            ],
            "selection": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 2,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 3,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 4,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 5,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 6,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 7,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 8,
                    "value": ""
                  }
            ]
        },
        "2": {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "question": "3 + ? = 10",
                    "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "question": "8 + ? = 15",
                    "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "question": "1 + ? = 6",
                    "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 5
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "question": "3 + ? = 6",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "question": "? - 9 = 3",
                    "options": [12, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 12
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "question": "? - 6 = 5",
                    "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 11
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "question": "8 - ? = 1",
                    "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "question": "4 - ? = 0",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 4
                }
            ],
            "selection": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 2,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 3,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 4,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 5,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 6,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 7,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 8,
                    "value": ""
                  }
            ]
        },
        "3": {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "question": "5 is more than 3 by _?",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "question": "2 more than 4 is _?",
                    "options": [6, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 6
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "question": "3 is more than 1 by_?",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "question": "8 more than 8 is _?",
                    "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 16
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "question": "8 is fewer than 9 by _?",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "question": "4 fewer than 6 is _?",
                    "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 10
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "question": "4 is fewer than 11 by_?",
                    "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "question": "3 fewer than 5 is _",
                    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 2
                }
            ],
            "selection": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 2,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 3,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 4,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 5,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 6,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 7,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 8,
                    "value": ""
                  }
            ]
        },
        "4": {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "question": "45 + 52 = ?",
                    "options": [97, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 97
                },
                {
                    "id": 2,
                    "question": "53 + 16 = ?",
                    "options": [69, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 69
                },
                {
                    "id": 3,
                    "question": "31 + 57 = ?",
                    "options": [88, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 88
                },
                {
                    "id": 4,
                    "question": "25 + 52 = ?",
                    "options": [77, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 77
                },
                {
                    "id": 5,
                    "question": "76 - 22 = ?",
                    "options": [54, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 54
                },
                {
                    "id": 6,
                    "question": "56 - 23 = ?",
                    "options": [33, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 33
                },
                {
                    "id": 7,
                    "question": "63 - 22 = ?",
                    "options": [41, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 41
                },
                {
                    "id": 8,
                    "question": "54 - 33 = ?",
                    "options": [21, 2, 3, 4],
                    "answer": 21
                }
            ],
            "selection": [
                {
                    "id": 1,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 2,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 3,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 4,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 5,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 6,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 7,
                    "value": ""
                  },
                  {
                    "id": 8,
                    "value": ""
                  }
            ]
        }
    },

    "Multiplication": {
      "1": {
          "questions": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "question": "1 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [2, 1, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 2
              },
              {
                  "id": 2,
                  "question": "2 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 4, 5],
                  "answer": 4
              },
              {
                  "id": 3,
                  "question": "3 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 6, 4],
                  "answer": 6
              },
              {
                  "id": 4,
                  "question": "4 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [8, 2, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 8
              },
              {
                  "id": 5,
                  "question": "5 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 3, 10],
                  "answer": 10
              },
              {
                  "id": 6,
                  "question": "6 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [12, 2, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 12
              },
              {
                  "id": 7,
                  "question": "7 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 3, 14],
                  "answer": 14
              },
              {
                  "id": 8,
                  "question": "8 * 2 = ?",
                  "options": [5, 16, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 16
              }
          ],
          "selection": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 2,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 3,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 4,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 5,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 6,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 7,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 8,
                  "value": ""
                }
          ]
      },
      "2": {
          "questions": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "question": "1 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [7, 2, 9, 4],
                  "answer": 9
              },
              {
                  "id": 2,
                  "question": "2 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [7, 2, 18, 4],
                  "answer": 18
              },
              {
                  "id": 3,
                  "question": "3 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [5, 27, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 27
              },
              {
                  "id": 4,
                  "question": "4 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 36, 4],
                  "answer": 36
              },
              {
                  "id": 5,
                  "question": "5 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [12, 2, 3, 45],
                  "answer": 45
              },
              {
                  "id": 6,
                  "question": "6 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [11, 2, 3, 54],
                  "answer": 54
              },
              {
                  "id": 7,
                  "question": "7 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [7, 2, 63, 4],
                  "answer": 63
              },
              {
                  "id": 8,
                  "question": "8 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 72, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 72
              }
          ],
          "selection": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 2,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 3,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 4,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 5,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 6,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 7,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 8,
                  "value": ""
                }
          ]
      },
      "3": {
          "questions": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "question": "5 * 4 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 20, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 20
              },
              {
                  "id": 2,
                  "question": "3 * 7 = ?",
                  "options": [6, 21, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 21
              },
              {
                  "id": 3,
                  "question": "8 * 4 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 32, 4],
                  "answer": 32
              },
              {
                  "id": 4,
                  "question": "6 * 6 = ?",
                  "options": [16, 2, 36, 4],
                  "answer": 36
              },
              {
                  "id": 5,
                  "question": "4 * 9 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 2, 36, 4],
                  "answer": 36
              },
              {
                  "id": 6,
                  "question": "3 * 8 = ?",
                  "options": [10, 24, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 24
              },
              {
                  "id": 7,
                  "question": "8 * 5 = ?",
                  "options": [7, 2, 3, 40],
                  "answer": 40
              },
              {
                  "id": 8,
                  "question": "3 * 7 = ?",
                  "options": [1, 27, 3, 4],
                  "answer": 27
              }
          ],
          "selection": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 2,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 3,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 4,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 5,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 6,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 7,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 8,
                  "value": ""
                }
          ]
      },
      "4": {
          "questions": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "question": "21 * 8 = ?",
                  "options": [97, 2, 168, 4],
                  "answer": 168
              },
              {
                  "id": 2,
                  "question": "89 * 78 = ?",
                  "options": [69, 2333, 312, 2262],
                  "answer": 2262
              },
              {
                  "id": 3,
                  "question": "66 * 57 = ?",
                  "options": [88, 2344, 3155, 3762],
                  "answer": 3762
              },
              {
                  "id": 4,
                  "question": "56 * 93 = ?",
                  "options": [77, 2334, 3112, 5208],
                  "answer": 5208
              },
              {
                  "id": 5,
                  "question": "96 * 8 = ?",
                  "options": [54, 2834, 768, 4234],
                  "answer": 768
              },
              {
                  "id": 6,
                  "question": "18 * 53 = ?",
                  "options": [33, 2466, 954, 4598],
                  "answer": 954
              },
              {
                  "id": 7,
                  "question": "23 * 63 = ?",
                  "options": [41, 2, 1449, 4],
                  "answer": 1449
              },
              {
                  "id": 8,
                  "question": "32 * 45 = ?",
                  "options": [21, 2498, 1440, 4788],
                  "answer": 1440
              }
          ],
          "selection": [
              {
                  "id": 1,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 2,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 3,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 4,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 5,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 6,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 7,
                  "value": ""
                },
                {
                  "id": 8,
                  "value": ""
                }
          ]
      }
  },

  "Decimal": {
    "1": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Which expression is the same as 4.902?",
                "options": ["(4×100)+(9×1/10​)+(2×1/1000​)",	"(4×100)+(9×1/10​)+(2×1/100​)",	"(4×10)+(9×1/10​)+(2×1/100​)", "(4×10)+(9×1/10​)+(2×1/1000​)"],
                "answer": "(4×100)+(9×1/10​)+(2×1/1000​)"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is (4×1,000)+(3×100)+(6×1/100​)+(7×1/1000​)?",
                "options": [4300.067,	8900.118,	63.3, 63.33],
                "answer": 4300.067
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "What is (5×100)+(8×1)+(2×1/10​)+(3×1/100​)+(1×1/1000​)?",
                "options": [508.231,	508.331,	508.3, 5008.3],
                "answer": 508.231
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "Which expression is the same as 1 ten, 3 ones, and 9 thousandths???",
                "options": [13.009,	13.0009,	13.00009, 13.000009],
                "answer": 13.009
            }
        ],
        "selection": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 2,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 3,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 4,
                "value": ""
              }
        ]
    },
    "2": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "What is 630.5 in words?",
                "options": ["Six hundred thirty and five tenths",	"Six hundred thirty and five ones",	"Six hundred three and five tenths", "Six hundred three and five tenths and eight ones"],
                "answer": "Six hundred thirty and five tenths"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "what is two and forty-two thousandths in decimal notation?",
                "options": [2.042,	0.242,	0.2042, 0.02042],
                "answer": 2.042
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "How many tenths are there in Ninety-eight and seventy-three hundredths?",
                "options": [9,	8,	7, 6],
                "answer": 9
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "How many thousandths are there in Ninety-eight and seventy-three hundredths?",
                "options": [730,	73,	7.3, 0.73],
                "answer": 730
            }
        ],
        "selection": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 2,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 3,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 4,
                "value": ""
              }
        ]
    },
    "3": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Which of the following have the same value as 18 ones and 302 thousandths?",
                "options": ["(1×10)+(8×1)+(3×1/10​)+(2×1/1,000​)",	"18302",	"11 ten + 8 ones + 3 tenths + 2 thousandths", "18303"],
                "answer": "(1×10)+(8×1)+(3×1/10​)+(2×1/1,000​)"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the expanded form of 6.017?",
                "options": ["6 + 1/100 + 7/1000",	"6 + 1/1000 + 7/10000",	"6 + 1/10 + 7/100", "6 + 1/10 + 6/100"],
                "answer": "6 + 1/100 + 7/1000"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "Which two of the following have the same value as 4.032?",
                "options": ["Four and thirty-two thousandths",	"4 ones + 3 tenths + 2 hundredths",	"4 ones + 3 tenths + 2 hundreds", "5 ones + 3 tenths + 2 hundreds"],
                "answer": "Four and thirty-two thousandths"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "What is the word form of 5.28",
                "options": ["Five and twenty-eight hundredths",	"Five and twenty-eight",	"Five and twenty-eight thousandths", "Five and twenty thousandths"],
                "answer": "Five and twenty-eight hundredths"
            }
        ],
        "selection": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 2,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 3,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 4,
                "value": ""
              }
        ]
    },
    "4": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "Round 0.698 to the nearest hundredth.",
                "options": [0.7,	0.69,	0.698, 0.666],
                "answer": 0.69
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "Round 0.698 to the nearest one.",
                "options": [1,	0.7,	0.74, 0.7400],
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "Round 0.698 to the nearest tenth.",
                "options": [0.7,	0.69,	0.698, 0.6980],
                "answer": 0.7
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "Round 0.698 to the nearest thousandth.",
                "options": [0.7,	0.69,	0.698, 0.6980],
                "answer": 698
            }
        ],
        "selection": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 2,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 3,
                "value": ""
              },
              {
                "id": 4,
                "value": ""
              }
        ]
    }
},

"Fraction": {
  "1": {
      "questions": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "question": "There are 3 balls outside during recess. 2 of the balls are orange. What fraction of balls are orange?",
              "options": ["5/8",	"7/8",	"4/8",	"2/3"],
              "answer": "2/3"
          },
          {
              "id": 2,
              "question": "Juanita cut her cheese into 4 equal pieces. She gave 2 pieces to her brother. What fraction of the cheese did Juanita give to her brother?",
              "options": ["4/8",	"5/8",	"7/8",	"6/8"],
              "answer": "4/8"
          },
          {
              "id": 3,
              "question": "Jeff has 7 blue balloons. He has 8 total balloons. What fraction of balloons are blue?",
              "options": ["7/8",	"4/8",	"5/8",	"6/8"],
              "answer": "7/8"
          },
          {
              "id": 4,
              "question": "Beth ate 6 pieces of a chocolate bar. The bar was split into 8 equal size pieces. What fraction of the chocolate bar did Beth eat?",
              "options": ["6/8",	"4/8",	"5/8",	"7/8"],
              "answer": "6/8"
          }
      ],
      "selection": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "value": ""
            }
      ]
  },
  "2": {
      "questions": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "question": "What does the numerator of the fraction 3/4 mean?",
              "options": ["We are counting 3 parts.",	"There are 4 parts per whole.",	"There is 3 parts per whole.", "There is 6 parts per whole.",	"The number of parts we are not counting"],
              "answer": "We are counting 3 parts."
          },
          {
              "id": 2,
              "question": "What does 5 represents in 5/2?",
              "options": ["The number of parts we are counting",	"The number of equal parts in all the wholes", "The number of equal parts in one whole",	"The number of parts we are not counting"],
              "answer": "The number of parts we are counting"
          },
          {
              "id": 3,
              "question": "What does the denominator of the fraction 2/6 mean?",
              "options": ["There are 6 parts per whole.",	"We are counting 6 parts.",	"We are counting 2 parts.",	"The number of parts we are not counting"],
              "answer": "There are 6 parts per whole."
          },
          {
              "id": 4,
              "question": "What does 8 represents in 5/8?",
              "options": ["The number of equal parts in one whole",	"The number of equal parts in all the wholes",	"The number of parts we are counting",	"The number of parts we are not counting"],
              "answer": "The number of equal parts in one whole"
          }
      ],
      "selection": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "value": ""
            }
      ]
  },
  "3": {
      "questions": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "question": "Which is the two fractions that are equal to 1?",
              "options": ["2 over 2",	"3 over 2",	"5 over 2", "7 over 2"],
              "answer": "2 over 2"
          },
          {
              "id": 2,
              "question": "Which is the two fractions that are equal to 1.5?",
              "options": ["3 over 2",	"4 over 2",	"5 over 2", "7 over 2"],
              "answer": "3 over 2"
          },
          {
              "id": 3,
              "question": "Which is the two fractions that are equal to 1.8?",
              "options": ["9 over 2",	"5 over 2",	"6 over 2", "7 over 2"],
              "answer": "9 over 2"
          },
          {
              "id": 4,
              "question": "Which is the two fractions that are equal to 2.5?",
              "options": ["5 over 2",	"3 over 2",	"1 over 2", "7 over 2"],
              "answer": "5 over 2"
          }
      ],
      "selection": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "value": ""
            }
      ]
  },
  "4": {
      "questions": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "question": "There are 2 apples in Sophie's lunch box. 1 of the apples is rotten. What fraction of apples are rotten?",
              "options": ["1 over 2",	"3 over 2",	"1 over 2", "7 over 2"],
              "answer": "1 over 2"
          },
          {
              "id": 2,
              "question": "Which fraction is greater than 5?",
              "options": ["625 over 5",	"5 over 5", "9 over 5", "7 over 2"],
              "answer": "625 over 5"
          },
          {
              "id": 3,
              "question": "What does the numerator of the fraction 1/8 mean?",
              "options": ["We are counting 1 part",	"We are counting 8 parts",	"We are not counting", "We are counting 7 parts"],
              "answer": "We are counting 1 part"
          },
          {
              "id": 4,
              "question": "Which fraction is greater than 2?",
              "options": ["4 over 1",	"4 over 2",	"2 over 2", "3 over 2"],
              "answer": 698
          }
      ],
      "selection": [
          {
              "id": 1,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 2,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 3,
              "value": ""
            },
            {
              "id": 4,
              "value": ""
            }
      ]
  }
}
}
